Kevin Flynn

Full-Stack Web Developer (NodeJS / VueJS)

London, UK
07796977257
flynny85@gmail.com
www.kubedev.co.uk
www.github.com/k-flynn-webdev

INTRO

A naturally curious problem solver. 10 years of experience in the games industry creating tools and improving workflow for artists and animators has given me a broad experience of day to day challenges and working in teams.

Being self driven and self taught has given me a different perspective and approach which sets me apart from most other developers.

PROJECTS

BS-Bingo Github.

A fun online multiplayer bingo game.

Daytrack **Github**.

Easy to use day journal app to help keep track of weekly/monthly progress.

Pomodoro Github.

A visually pleasing PWA timer app.

EXPERIENCE

Self — Web Development

July 2018 - Present Learning full-stack development

Freelance — Technical Animator

Jan 2017 - Jan 2018

Freelance: Animator-Setup-Tools

22 Cans, Guildford, UK — Technical Animator

July 2015 - Jan 2017

Mobile titles : Animator-Setup-Tools

If You Can, London, UK — Technical Animator

May 2013 - March 2015

Mobile titles: Animator-Setup-Tools

Traveller's Tales, Wilmslow, UK — Technical Animator

Jun 2008 - Apr 2013 Mobile titles: Animator

SKILLS

- Design/Mockup
- Html/CSS/Javascript
- Responsive Design
- Animation (3d)

TECHNOLOGIES

- NodeJS (ExpressJS)
- VueJS
- MongoDB
- Nginx
- VPS Deploy
- TDD (Jest/Mocha/Chai)
- Unity
- C# (Unity)
- Python

EDUCATION

The University of Bolton

2002 - 2006 BA Graphic Design & Illustration